<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HEMB</title>
    <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HEMB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://defjm.github.io/hemb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI user experience</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/2040305_ai-user-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/2040305_ai-user-experience/</guid>
      <description>We need to think more about user experience and usability for designing AI applications AI applications are different from conventional software systems. This has implications for user experience and usability.
Developers need to understand the effects of probabilistic model outputs. For example, what impact has a chatbot answer if it contains a hallucination? This is highly dependent on the given use case. It may be no problem if the chatbot is used to brainstorm design ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTFs on AI? - Part 1: LLM Prompt Injection Attacks - Gandalf &amp; LLM CTF SaTML 2024</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240127_ctf-llm-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240127_ctf-llm-part1/</guid>
      <description>Capture the Flag competitions on Large Language Models Capture the flag competitions are a great way of learning cybersecurity concepts and tools. There is an introductory article on CTFs by Hack The Box, in which they define CTFs as follows:
A CTF (aka Capture the Flag) is a competition where teams or individuals have to solve several Challenges. The one that solves/collects most flags the fastest wins the competition.
Applying this concept to large language models and chatbots is a recent and interesting development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on the Hugo PaperMod theme</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240123_hugo-papermod-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240123_hugo-papermod-setup/</guid>
      <description>Summary This website uses the Hugo PaperMod theme. You can find few debugging and research notes below.
Search Debugging When setting up the website, we had a few bugs with PaperMod&amp;rsquo;s search functionality.
There is a small wiki section on search. If you use languages in your config.yaml (or hugo.yaml), make sure you name the search file content/search.en.md. Related post Search calibration and algorithm Current parameters for search:
fuseOpts: isCaseSensitive: false includeScore: false shouldSort: true location: 0 distance: 1000 threshold: 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/about/</guid>
      <description>Who we are DefJM https://github.com/defjm/ real.defjm@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Operator DefJM real.defjm@gmail.com
In case of problems, questions or suggestions regarding this site, please contact the above e-mail address. Any reproduction and other use of the entire website and/or copyrighted parts of this website, in particular sound and image material, photos, texts, graphics, layouts, is – unless expressly stated otherwise – not permitted. Regarding the liability of the operator, please refer to the disclaimer.
This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
