<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on HEMB</title>
    <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on HEMB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On productive writing</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20241006_productive-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20241006_productive-writing/</guid>
      <description>Writing a paper or dissertation can be very hard. I have had several students going through what they experienced as a daunting challenge. When asking for advise, I used to tell them that I, too, struggled. And I shared bits and pieces how I managed. Last week I finally wrote up those pieces as a whole.
TLDR: My main advise is to work in time-boxed writing blocks. In each block, you stick to only one writing mode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-AI-Interaction: We need to think more about AI usability</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240305_ai-user-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240305_ai-user-experience/</guid>
      <description>AI systems are different from conventional software systems. And this matters. In my job to develop and implement machine learning and AI services for multiple industrial use cases. As we deal with related quality and security challenges, it has become clear to me that we need to spend more time thinking through the user experience (UX) of these systems. They are different from conventional software systems and this has implications for usability and design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTFs on AI? - Part 1: LLM Prompt Injection Attacks - Gandalf &amp; LLM CTF SaTML 2024</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240127_ctf-llm-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240127_ctf-llm-part1/</guid>
      <description>Capture the Flag competitions on Large Language Models Capture the flag competitions are a great way of learning cybersecurity concepts and tools. There is an introductory article on CTFs by Hack The Box, in which they define CTFs as follows:
A CTF (aka Capture the Flag) is a competition where teams or individuals have to solve several Challenges. The one that solves/collects most flags the fastest wins the competition.
Applying this concept to large language models and chatbots is a recent and interesting development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on the Hugo PaperMod theme</title>
      <link>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240123_hugo-papermod-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://defjm.github.io/hemb/posts/20240123_hugo-papermod-setup/</guid>
      <description>Summary This website uses the Hugo PaperMod theme. You can find few debugging and research notes below.
Search Debugging When setting up the website, we had a few bugs with PaperMod&amp;rsquo;s search functionality.
There is a small wiki section on search. If you use languages in your config.yaml (or hugo.yaml), make sure you name the search file content/search.en.md. Related post Search calibration and algorithm Current parameters for search:
fuseOpts: isCaseSensitive: false includeScore: false shouldSort: true location: 0 distance: 1000 threshold: 0.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
